What's your specialty today?
How are you today? Nice to meet you.
Hello everybody, that's a nice beautiful looking group of people.
So I know this menu better than you do, okay?
I probably know it better than anybody in here.
That's East Palestine, Ohio. You know, where the train derailed.
And that's them, happy as a chemically mutated clam,
to see the man that put they town in this situation with the train derailment.
And bragged about it!
Remember when he said this?
I am continuing to get rid of costly and unnecessary regulations.
Much work left to do, but effect will be great.
Business and jobs will grow.
You know what?
This feels eerily like when we watched all the racism in Ukraine,
when the war started and we were supposed to be caring about Ukraine,
but it was like, ooh, y'all racist.
I'm looking at this like, if y'all love this man so bad,
when he hurt you so bad, baby, I got to look the other way.
Let me know when you're ready to heal.
Let me go ahead and put my energy back to Palestine, Palestine.